1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. custom.BrowserHelper.setupBrowserWindow()
33. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
37. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
41. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
45. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
49. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
53. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
57. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_My Address"), 4)
61. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_My Address"))
65. editBtn = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject()
69. editBtn.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, "(//button[contains(.,'Edit')])[1]")
73. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/btn_Edit"))
77. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_First Name"), 10)
81. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_First Name"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
85. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
89. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Last Name"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
93. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
97. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Mobile Phone"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
101. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Mobile Phone"), randomPhone)
105. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_E-mail"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
109. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_E-mail"), randomEmail)
113. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Address"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
117. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_Address"), randomAddress)
121. clearText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_ZipPostal Code"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
125. setText(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/Field_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
129. click(findTestObject("Address Management/Edit Address/button_Save"))
133. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Address Management/Shipping Address/lbl_Shipping Address"), 10)
137. verifyName = new com.kms.katalon.core.testobject.TestObject()
141. verifyName.addProperty("xpath", EQUALS, //*[contains(text(),'$randomFirstName')])
145. verifyElementPresent(verifyName, 10)
1. status = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
5. if (status == "PASSED")
2. saveScreenshot("FAILED")
1. tcName = getTestCaseName()
1. return com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getExecutionSourceName().replace(Test Cases/, ).replaceAll([\\/:*?"<>|], _)
5. folderPath = Screenshot/$status/$tcName/
9. Files.createDirectories(Paths.get(folderPath))
13. screenshotPath = $folderPath$status_$this.getTimestamp().png
1. return new java.text.SimpleDateFormat(yyyyMMdd_HHmmss).format(new java.util.Date())
17. takeScreenshot(screenshotPath)
21. println("Screenshot saved : " + screenshotPath)